export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "I often make decisions based on:",
    options: [
      { label: "Logic and facts", value: "Logic and facts" },
      { label: "Intuition and feelings", value: "Intuition and feelings" },
      { label: "A combination of both", value: "A combination of both" },
      { label: "None of the above", value: "None of the above" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A combination of both",
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "When faced with a problem, I usually:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Analyze the situation thoroughly",
        value: "Analyze the situation thoroughly",
      },
      {
        label: "Rely on my instincts to guide me",
        value: "Rely on my instincts to guide me",
      },
      { label: "Seek advice from others", value: "Seek advice from others" },
      { label: "Avoid confronting it", value: "Avoid confronting it" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Analyze the situation thoroughly",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "I prefer working in a team setting when:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I can contribute my ideas and collaborate",
        value: "I can contribute my ideas and collaborate",
      },
      {
        label: "I can lead and direct others",
        value: "I can lead and direct others",
      },
      { label: "I can work independently", value: "I can work independently" },
      {
        label: "I avoid working with others",
        value: "I avoid working with others",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I can contribute my ideas and collaborate",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "When under stress, I am most likely to:",
    options: [
      { label: "Stay calm and focused", value: "Stay calm and focused" },
      {
        label: "Seek emotional support from others",
        value: "Seek emotional support from others",
      },
      {
        label: "Retreat and deal with it alone",
        value: "Retreat and deal with it alone",
      },
      { label: "React impulsively", value: "React impulsively" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stay calm and focused",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "In social situations, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Enjoy meeting new people and making friends",
        value: "Enjoy meeting new people and making friends",
      },
      {
        label: "Prefer spending time alone or with a few close friends",
        value: "Prefer spending time alone or with a few close friends",
      },
      {
        label: "Adapt to different social settings easily",
        value: "Adapt to different social settings easily",
      },
      {
        label: "Feel uncomfortable and shy away",
        value: "Feel uncomfortable and shy away",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Enjoy meeting new people and making friends",
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "When faced with a challenge, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Take immediate action to resolve it",
        value: "Take immediate action to resolve it",
      },
      {
        label: "Assess the situation before deciding on a plan",
        value: "Assess the situation before deciding on a plan",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek help and guidance from others",
        value: "Seek help and guidance from others",
      },
      { label: "Avoid dealing with it", value: "Avoid dealing with it" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Assess the situation before deciding on a plan",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "I believe success is mostly attributed to:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Hard work and perseverance",
        value: "Hard work and perseverance",
      },
      { label: "Luck and chance", value: "Luck and chance" },
      {
        label: "Having the right connections",
        value: "Having the right connections",
      },
      {
        label: "Talent and natural ability",
        value: "Talent and natural ability",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hard work and perseverance",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "When learning a new skill or subject, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label:
          "Follow a structured approach and seek to understand concepts deeply",
        value:
          "Follow a structured approach and seek to understand concepts deeply",
      },
      {
        label: "Experiment and learn through trial and error",
        value: "Experiment and learn through trial and error",
      },
      {
        label: "Ask questions and seek clarification from experts",
        value: "Ask questions and seek clarification from experts",
      },
      {
        label: "Learn best when taught by others",
        value: "Learn best when taught by others",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Follow a structured approach and seek to understand concepts deeply",
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "My friends would describe me as:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Analytical and detail-oriented",
        value: "Analytical and detail-oriented",
      },
      { label: "Empathetic and caring", value: "Empathetic and caring" },
      { label: "Confident and assertive", value: "Confident and assertive" },
      { label: "Adaptable and easygoing", value: "Adaptable and easygoing" },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Analytical and detail-oriented",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "I find it easiest to communicate when:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I can explain my ideas clearly and logically",
        value: "I can explain my ideas clearly and logically",
      },
      {
        label: "I can relate to others emotionally",
        value: "I can relate to others emotionally",
      },
      {
        label: "I can use visuals or hands-on demonstrations",
        value: "I can use visuals or hands-on demonstrations",
      },
      {
        label: "I can listen actively and provide feedback",
        value: "I can listen actively and provide feedback",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I can explain my ideas clearly and logically",
  },
  //    Interest Inventory
  {
    id: 11,
    question: "I find it most fulfilling to spend my time:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Engaging in creative activities.",
        value: "Engaging in creative activities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Learning about new technologies.",
        value: "Learning about new technologies.",
      },
      {
        label: "Helping others with their problems.",
        value: "Helping others with their problems.",
      },
      {
        label: "Analyzing data and finding patterns.",
        value: "Analyzing data and finding patterns.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Engaging in creative activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 12,
    question: "Which activity would you prefer during your free time?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Reading a book or watching a documentary.",
        value: "Reading a book or watching a documentary.",
      },
      {
        label: "Participating in a community service project.",
        value: "Participating in a community service project.",
      },
      {
        label: "Engaging in a physical sport or outdoor activity.",
        value: "Engaging in a physical sport or outdoor activity.",
      },
      {
        label: "Attending a workshop to learn a new skill.",
        value: "Attending a workshop to learn a new skill.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Reading a book or watching a documentary.",
  },
  {
    id: 13,
    question: "What type of environment do you thrive in?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "A structured and predictable environment.",
        value: "A structured and predictable environment.",
      },
      {
        label: "A dynamic and fast-paced environment.",
        value: "A dynamic and fast-paced environment.",
      },
      {
        label: "A collaborative and team-oriented environment.",
        value: "A collaborative and team-oriented environment.",
      },
      {
        label: "An independent and self-directed environment.",
        value: "An independent and self-directed environment.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A dynamic and fast-paced environment.",
  },
  {
    id: 14,
    question: "Which of these interests you the most?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Creating or designing something new.",
        value: "Creating or designing something new.",
      },
      {
        label: "Solving complex problems or puzzles.",
        value: "Solving complex problems or puzzles.",
      },
      {
        label: "Organizing and leading a project.",
        value: "Organizing and leading a project.",
      },
      {
        label: "Helping others achieve their goals.",
        value: "Helping others achieve their goals.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Creating or designing something new.",
  },
  {
    id: 15,
    question: "What kind of activities make you lose track of time?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Working on a challenging technical problem.",
        value: "Working on a challenging technical problem.",
      },
      {
        label: "Helping friends or colleagues with their issues.",
        value: "Helping friends or colleagues with their issues.",
      },
      {
        label: "Experimenting with new ideas and concepts.",
        value: "Experimenting with new ideas and concepts.",
      },
      {
        label: "Organizing tasks and planning ahead.",
        value: "Organizing tasks and planning ahead.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Experimenting with new ideas and concepts.",
  },

  // Personality Traits
  {
    id: 16,
    question: "I would describe my personality as:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Introverted and thoughtful.",
        value: "Introverted and thoughtful.",
      },
      {
        label: "Extroverted and outgoing.",
        value: "Extroverted and outgoing.",
      },
      {
        label: "Analytical and detail-oriented.",
        value: "Analytical and detail-oriented.",
      },
      {
        label: "Empathetic and compassionate.",
        value: "Empathetic and compassionate.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Analytical and detail-oriented.",
  },
  {
    id: 17,
    question: "When faced with a stressful situation, I tend to:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Stay calm and find a solution.",
        value: "Stay calm and find a solution.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek support from friends or family.",
        value: "Seek support from friends or family.",
      },
      {
        label: "Withdraw and handle it on my own.",
        value: "Withdraw and handle it on my own.",
      },
      {
        label: "React impulsively and emotionally.",
        value: "React impulsively and emotionally.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Stay calm and find a solution.",
  },
  {
    id: 18,
    question: "Which of these best describes your approach to problem-solving?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I analyze all the details before making a decision.",
        value: "I analyze all the details before making a decision.",
      },
      {
        label: "I trust my instincts and make quick decisions.",
        value: "I trust my instincts and make quick decisions.",
      },
      {
        label: "I collaborate with others to find a solution.",
        value: "I collaborate with others to find a solution.",
      },
      {
        label: "I avoid making decisions until absolutely necessary.",
        value: "I avoid making decisions until absolutely necessary.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I analyze all the details before making a decision.",
  },
  {
    id: 19,
    question: "How do you typically react to change?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I embrace it and adapt quickly.",
        value: "I embrace it and adapt quickly.",
      },
      {
        label: "I resist it and prefer stability.",
        value: "I resist it and prefer stability.",
      },
      {
        label: "I analyze the pros and cons before accepting it.",
        value: "I analyze the pros and cons before accepting it.",
      },
      {
        label: "I seek reassurance from others before moving forward.",
        value: "I seek reassurance from others before moving forward.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I embrace it and adapt quickly.",
  },
  {
    id: 20,
    question: "Which of the following describes your typical work style?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I am highly organized and methodical.",
        value: "I am highly organized and methodical.",
      },
      {
        label: "I am flexible and adapt to changing situations.",
        value: "I am flexible and adapt to changing situations.",
      },
      {
        label: "I work best under pressure.",
        value: "I work best under pressure.",
      },
      {
        label: "I prefer to work independently.",
        value: "I prefer to work independently.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I am highly organized and methodical.",
  },

  // Skills and Competencies
  {
    id: 21,
    question: "Which skill do you consider your strongest?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Critical thinking and problem-solving.",
        value: "Critical thinking and problem-solving.",
      },
      { label: "Effective communication.", value: "Effective communication." },
      {
        label: "Time management and organization.",
        value: "Time management and organization.",
      },
      {
        label: "Collaboration and teamwork.",
        value: "Collaboration and teamwork.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Critical thinking and problem-solving.",
  },
  {
    id: 22,
    question: "When learning a new skill, I usually:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Follow a step-by-step process.",
        value: "Follow a step-by-step process.",
      },
      {
        label: "Learn through hands-on experience.",
        value: "Learn through hands-on experience.",
      },
      {
        label: "Prefer to be guided by an expert.",
        value: "Prefer to be guided by an expert.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek out relevant information on my own.",
        value: "Seek out relevant information on my own.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Learn through hands-on experience.",
  },
  {
    id: 23,
    question: "Which of these competencies do you value most in a workplace?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Technical expertise and knowledge.",
        value: "Technical expertise and knowledge.",
      },
      {
        label: "Interpersonal and communication skills.",
        value: "Interpersonal and communication skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "Leadership and management skills.",
        value: "Leadership and management skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "Adaptability and flexibility.",
        value: "Adaptability and flexibility.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Interpersonal and communication skills.",
  },
  {
    id: 24,
    question: "How do you approach complex tasks?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Break them down into smaller, manageable steps.",
        value: "Break them down into smaller, manageable steps.",
      },
      {
        label: "Tackle them head-on and adjust as I go.",
        value: "Tackle them head-on and adjust as I go.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek advice from others before starting.",
        value: "Seek advice from others before starting.",
      },
      {
        label: "Procrastinate until the last minute.",
        value: "Procrastinate until the last minute.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Break them down into smaller, manageable steps.",
  },
  {
    id: 25,
    question: "In terms of professional development, I prioritize:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Gaining new technical skills.",
        value: "Gaining new technical skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "Improving my leadership abilities.",
        value: "Improving my leadership abilities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Enhancing my communication skills.",
        value: "Enhancing my communication skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "Building a strong professional network.",
        value: "Building a strong professional network.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Gaining new technical skills.",
  },

  // Work Values
  {
    id: 26,
    question: "What motivates you the most at work?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Opportunities for advancement.",
        value: "Opportunities for advancement.",
      },
      {
        label: "A sense of purpose and impact.",
        value: "A sense of purpose and impact.",
      },
      {
        label: "Financial rewards and recognition.",
        value: "Financial rewards and recognition.",
      },
      {
        label: "A positive and supportive work environment.",
        value: "A positive and supportive work environment.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A sense of purpose and impact.",
  },
  {
    id: 27,
    question: "Which of these work values is most important to you?",
    options: [
      { label: "Work-life balance.", value: "Work-life balance." },
      { label: "Job security.", value: "Job security." },
      {
        label: "Professional growth opportunities.",
        value: "Professional growth opportunities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Recognition for your contributions.",
        value: "Recognition for your contributions.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Work-life balance.",
  },
  {
    id: 28,
    question: "How important is company culture in your job satisfaction?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Extremely important, it defines my work experience.",
        value: "Extremely important, it defines my work experience.",
      },
      {
        label: "Somewhat important, but not the most critical factor.",
        value: "Somewhat important, but not the most critical factor.",
      },
      {
        label: "Neutral, I can adapt to different cultures.",
        value: "Neutral, I can adapt to different cultures.",
      },
      {
        label: "Not important, I focus more on the job itself.",
        value: "Not important, I focus more on the job itself.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Extremely important, it defines my work experience.",
  },
  {
    id: 29,
    question: "What do you value most in a supervisor or manager?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Clear communication and guidance.",
        value: "Clear communication and guidance.",
      },
      {
        label: "Support for my professional development.",
        value: "Support for my professional development.",
      },
      {
        label: "Recognition of my efforts and achievements.",
        value: "Recognition of my efforts and achievements.",
      },
      {
        label: "Flexibility and understanding.",
        value: "Flexibility and understanding.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Support for my professional development.",
  },
  {
    id: 30,
    question: "When considering a new job, the most critical factor for me is:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "The salary and benefits package.",
        value: "The salary and benefits package.",
      },
      {
        label: "The work-life balance offered.",
        value: "The work-life balance offered.",
      },
      {
        label: "The opportunities for career growth.",
        value: "The opportunities for career growth.",
      },
      {
        label: "The company’s values and mission.",
        value: "The company’s values and mission.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The opportunities for career growth.",
  },

  // Motivations
  {
    id: 31,
    question: "What drives you to achieve your goals?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "A desire for personal fulfillment.",
        value: "A desire for personal fulfillment.",
      },
      {
        label: "The need for financial security.",
        value: "The need for financial security.",
      },
      {
        label: "Recognition from peers and superiors.",
        value: "Recognition from peers and superiors.",
      },
      {
        label: "The challenge of overcoming obstacles.",
        value: "The challenge of overcoming obstacles.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The challenge of overcoming obstacles.",
  },
  {
    id: 32,
    question: "Which of the following best describes your motivation at work?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I am motivated by setting and achieving goals.",
        value: "I am motivated by setting and achieving goals.",
      },
      {
        label: "I am driven by the desire to learn new things.",
        value: "I am driven by the desire to learn new things.",
      },
      {
        label: "I am motivated by helping others succeed.",
        value: "I am motivated by helping others succeed.",
      },
      {
        label: "I am driven by financial rewards and benefits.",
        value: "I am driven by financial rewards and benefits.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I am motivated by setting and achieving goals.",
  },
  {
    id: 33,
    question: "How do you stay motivated during difficult tasks?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I remind myself of the end goal.",
        value: "I remind myself of the end goal.",
      },
      {
        label: "I take breaks and recharge.",
        value: "I take breaks and recharge.",
      },
      {
        label: "I seek encouragement from others.",
        value: "I seek encouragement from others.",
      },
      {
        label: "I push through until it's done.",
        value: "I push through until it's done.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I remind myself of the end goal.",
  },
  {
    id: 34,
    question: "What motivates you to take on new challenges?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "The opportunity to learn and grow.",
        value: "The opportunity to learn and grow.",
      },
      {
        label: "The chance to prove my abilities.",
        value: "The chance to prove my abilities.",
      },
      {
        label: "The potential for rewards and recognition.",
        value: "The potential for rewards and recognition.",
      },
      {
        label: "The excitement of trying something new.",
        value: "The excitement of trying something new.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The opportunity to learn and grow.",
  },
  {
    id: 35,
    question:
      "Which of these is most likely to keep you motivated in the long term?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Achieving work-life balance.",
        value: "Achieving work-life balance.",
      },
      {
        label: "Consistent professional development.",
        value: "Consistent professional development.",
      },
      {
        label: "Regular recognition and rewards.",
        value: "Regular recognition and rewards.",
      },
      {
        label: "A strong sense of purpose and meaning.",
        value: "A strong sense of purpose and meaning.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A strong sense of purpose and meaning.",
  },

  // Decision-Making Style
  {
    id: 36,
    question: "When making decisions, I typically:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Rely on logical analysis and facts.",
        value: "Rely on logical analysis and facts.",
      },
      {
        label: "Trust my intuition and feelings.",
        value: "Trust my intuition and feelings.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek advice and input from others.",
        value: "Seek advice and input from others.",
      },
      {
        label: "Avoid making decisions until absolutely necessary.",
        value: "Avoid making decisions until absolutely necessary.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Rely on logical analysis and facts.",
  },
  {
    id: 37,
    question: "How do you usually approach important decisions?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I gather all relevant information before deciding.",
        value: "I gather all relevant information before deciding.",
      },
      {
        label: "I go with my gut feeling.",
        value: "I go with my gut feeling.",
      },
      {
        label: "I consult with trusted advisors.",
        value: "I consult with trusted advisors.",
      },
      {
        label: "I weigh the pros and cons.",
        value: "I weigh the pros and cons.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I gather all relevant information before deciding.",
  },
  {
    id: 38,
    question: "Which factor influences your decision-making the most?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Potential risks and rewards.",
        value: "Potential risks and rewards.",
      },
      { label: "The opinions of others.", value: "The opinions of others." },
      {
        label: "Personal values and beliefs.",
        value: "Personal values and beliefs.",
      },
      { label: "Past experiences.", value: "Past experiences." },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Potential risks and rewards.",
  },
  {
    id: 39,
    question: "In a group setting, I tend to:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Take the lead in decision-making.",
        value: "Take the lead in decision-making.",
      },
      {
        label: "Encourage group consensus.",
        value: "Encourage group consensus.",
      },
      {
        label: "Provide input but let others decide.",
        value: "Provide input but let others decide.",
      },
      {
        label: "Step back and observe the process.",
        value: "Step back and observe the process.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Encourage group consensus.",
  },
  {
    id: 40,
    question: "How do you handle decisions when under pressure?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I stay calm and focus on facts.",
        value: "I stay calm and focus on facts.",
      },
      {
        label: "I rely on my instincts to guide me.",
        value: "I rely on my instincts to guide me.",
      },
      {
        label: "I seek quick input from others.",
        value: "I seek quick input from others.",
      },
      {
        label: "I avoid making a decision until the last moment.",
        value: "I avoid making a decision until the last moment.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I stay calm and focus on facts.",
  },

  // Interpersonal Skills
  {
    id: 41,
    question: "How do you typically handle conflict in a team?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I address it directly and seek a resolution.",
        value: "I address it directly and seek a resolution.",
      },
      {
        label: "I try to mediate and find common ground.",
        value: "I try to mediate and find common ground.",
      },
      {
        label: "I avoid it and hope it resolves itself.",
        value: "I avoid it and hope it resolves itself.",
      },
      {
        label: "I take sides based on who I agree with.",
        value: "I take sides based on who I agree with.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I try to mediate and find common ground.",
  },
  {
    id: 42,
    question: "Which of these best describes your communication style?",
    options: [
      { label: "Direct and to the point.", value: "Direct and to the point." },
      {
        label: "Empathetic and understanding.",
        value: "Empathetic and understanding.",
      },
      {
        label: "Assertive but respectful.",
        value: "Assertive but respectful.",
      },
      { label: "Reserved and thoughtful.", value: "Reserved and thoughtful." },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Assertive but respectful.",
  },
  {
    id: 43,
    question: "How do you typically respond to feedback?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I welcome it and use it to improve.",
        value: "I welcome it and use it to improve.",
      },
      {
        label: "I appreciate it but don't always act on it.",
        value: "I appreciate it but don't always act on it.",
      },
      {
        label: "I feel defensive but try to take it in stride.",
        value: "I feel defensive but try to take it in stride.",
      },
      {
        label: "I tend to ignore it and stick to my own ways.",
        value: "I tend to ignore it and stick to my own ways.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I welcome it and use it to improve.",
  },
  {
    id: 44,
    question: "How do you build relationships with new colleagues?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I make an effort to connect personally.",
        value: "I make an effort to connect personally.",
      },
      {
        label: "I focus on work-related interactions first.",
        value: "I focus on work-related interactions first.",
      },
      {
        label: "I wait for them to approach me.",
        value: "I wait for them to approach me.",
      },
      {
        label: "I keep things strictly professional.",
        value: "I keep things strictly professional.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I make an effort to connect personally.",
  },
  {
    id: 45,
    question: "How do you handle misunderstandings at work?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I clarify the issue and seek to resolve it.",
        value: "I clarify the issue and seek to resolve it.",
      },
      { label: "I let it go and move on.", value: "I let it go and move on." },
      {
        label: "I discuss it privately with the person involved.",
        value: "I discuss it privately with the person involved.",
      },
      {
        label: "I bring it up in a team meeting for discussion.",
        value: "I bring it up in a team meeting for discussion.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I clarify the issue and seek to resolve it.",
  },

  // Leadership
  {
    id: 46,
    question: "Which of the following best describes your leadership style?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Authoritative and directive.",
        value: "Authoritative and directive.",
      },
      {
        label: "Democratic and inclusive.",
        value: "Democratic and inclusive.",
      },
      {
        label: "Transformational and inspiring.",
        value: "Transformational and inspiring.",
      },
      {
        label: "Hands-off and delegative.",
        value: "Hands-off and delegative.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Democratic and inclusive.",
  },
  {
    id: 47,
    question: "How do you motivate your team members?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "By setting clear goals and expectations.",
        value: "By setting clear goals and expectations.",
      },
      {
        label: "By recognizing and rewarding their efforts.",
        value: "By recognizing and rewarding their efforts.",
      },
      {
        label: "By leading by example and working alongside them.",
        value: "By leading by example and working alongside them.",
      },
      {
        label: "By giving them autonomy and trust.",
        value: "By giving them autonomy and trust.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "By recognizing and rewarding their efforts.",
  },
  {
    id: 48,
    question: "When leading a project, I prefer to:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Delegate tasks and oversee progress.",
        value: "Delegate tasks and oversee progress.",
      },
      {
        label: "Involve the team in decision-making.",
        value: "Involve the team in decision-making.",
      },
      {
        label: "Take charge and make key decisions myself.",
        value: "Take charge and make key decisions myself.",
      },
      {
        label: "Allow the team to self-manage.",
        value: "Allow the team to self-manage.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Involve the team in decision-making.",
  },
  {
    id: 49,
    question: "How do you handle underperformance in your team?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Address it directly and set improvement goals.",
        value: "Address it directly and set improvement goals.",
      },
      {
        label: "Provide additional support and training.",
        value: "Provide additional support and training.",
      },
      {
        label: "Give constructive feedback and encourage improvement.",
        value: "Give constructive feedback and encourage improvement.",
      },
      {
        label: "Reassign tasks or roles as needed.",
        value: "Reassign tasks or roles as needed.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Give constructive feedback and encourage improvement.",
  },
  {
    id: 50,
    question: "Which quality do you consider most important in a leader?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Vision and strategic thinking.",
        value: "Vision and strategic thinking.",
      },
      {
        label: "Empathy and understanding.",
        value: "Empathy and understanding.",
      },
      {
        label: "Decisiveness and confidence.",
        value: "Decisiveness and confidence.",
      },
      { label: "Integrity and honesty.", value: "Integrity and honesty." },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Vision and strategic thinking.",
  },
  {
    id: 51,
    question: "How do you foster teamwork and collaboration?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Encourage open communication and idea-sharing.",
        value: "Encourage open communication and idea-sharing.",
      },
      {
        label: "Organize team-building activities.",
        value: "Organize team-building activities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Set clear roles and responsibilities.",
        value: "Set clear roles and responsibilities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Lead by example and demonstrate collaboration.",
        value: "Lead by example and demonstrate collaboration.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Encourage open communication and idea-sharing.",
  },
  {
    id: 52,
    question: "When dealing with a difficult decision as a leader, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Consult with my team before deciding.",
        value: "Consult with my team before deciding.",
      },
      {
        label: "Trust my own judgment and make the call.",
        value: "Trust my own judgment and make the call.",
      },
      {
        label: "Consider the potential impact on all stakeholders.",
        value: "Consider the potential impact on all stakeholders.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek advice from a mentor or senior leader.",
        value: "Seek advice from a mentor or senior leader.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Consider the potential impact on all stakeholders.",
  },

  // Work-Life Balance
  {
    id: 53,
    question: "How do you maintain work-life balance?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "By setting clear boundaries between work and personal life.",
        value: "By setting clear boundaries between work and personal life.",
      },
      {
        label: "By prioritizing my tasks and managing time effectively.",
        value: "By prioritizing my tasks and managing time effectively.",
      },
      {
        label: "By taking regular breaks and vacations.",
        value: "By taking regular breaks and vacations.",
      },
      {
        label: "By staying flexible and adjusting as needed.",
        value: "By staying flexible and adjusting as needed.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "By setting clear boundaries between work and personal life.",
  },
  {
    id: 54,
    question: "What do you do to recharge after a busy workweek?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Spend time with family and friends.",
        value: "Spend time with family and friends.",
      },
      {
        label: "Engage in hobbies or physical activities.",
        value: "Engage in hobbies or physical activities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Relax and unwind at home.",
        value: "Relax and unwind at home.",
      },
      {
        label: "Focus on personal projects or goals.",
        value: "Focus on personal projects or goals.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Engage in hobbies or physical activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 55,
    question: "How important is work-life balance to you?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Extremely important, it affects my overall well-being.",
        value: "Extremely important, it affects my overall well-being.",
      },
      {
        label: "Important, but I can adjust when necessary.",
        value: "Important, but I can adjust when necessary.",
      },
      {
        label: "Somewhat important, but not a top priority.",
        value: "Somewhat important, but not a top priority.",
      },
      {
        label: "Not very important, I focus more on work.",
        value: "Not very important, I focus more on work.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Extremely important, it affects my overall well-being.",
  },
  {
    id: 56,
    question: "When work becomes overwhelming, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Take a break and step away for a bit.",
        value: "Take a break and step away for a bit.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek support from colleagues or friends.",
        value: "Seek support from colleagues or friends.",
      },
      {
        label: "Focus on one task at a time to regain control.",
        value: "Focus on one task at a time to regain control.",
      },
      {
        label: "Push through and keep working until it's done.",
        value: "Push through and keep working until it's done.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Take a break and step away for a bit.",
  },
  {
    id: 57,
    question: "What strategies do you use to avoid burnout?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Maintain a healthy work-life balance.",
        value: "Maintain a healthy work-life balance.",
      },
      {
        label: "Engage in regular physical activity.",
        value: "Engage in regular physical activity.",
      },
      {
        label: "Practice mindfulness and stress management techniques.",
        value: "Practice mindfulness and stress management techniques.",
      },
      {
        label: "Set realistic expectations and goals.",
        value: "Set realistic expectations and goals.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Maintain a healthy work-life balance.",
  },

  // Adaptability
  {
    id: 58,
    question: "How do you typically respond to unexpected changes at work?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I adapt quickly and find a new way forward.",
        value: "I adapt quickly and find a new way forward.",
      },
      {
        label: "I analyze the situation before taking action.",
        value: "I analyze the situation before taking action.",
      },
      {
        label: "I seek guidance from others on how to proceed.",
        value: "I seek guidance from others on how to proceed.",
      },
      {
        label: "I feel stressed but eventually adapt.",
        value: "I feel stressed but eventually adapt.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I adapt quickly and find a new way forward.",
  },
  {
    id: 59,
    question: "When faced with a new challenge, I:",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Embrace it as an opportunity to grow.",
        value: "Embrace it as an opportunity to grow.",
      },
      {
        label: "Take time to evaluate my options.",
        value: "Take time to evaluate my options.",
      },
      {
        label: "Look for support or resources to help me.",
        value: "Look for support or resources to help me.",
      },
      {
        label: "Feel anxious but push through it.",
        value: "Feel anxious but push through it.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Embrace it as an opportunity to grow.",
  },
  {
    id: 60,
    question:
      "How do you handle situations where you lack the necessary skills?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "I seek out learning opportunities to build the skills.",
        value: "I seek out learning opportunities to build the skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "I collaborate with others who have the skills.",
        value: "I collaborate with others who have the skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "I find ways to work around the skill gap.",
        value: "I find ways to work around the skill gap.",
      },
      {
        label: "I ask for guidance or mentorship.",
        value: "I ask for guidance or mentorship.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "I seek out learning opportunities to build the skills.",
  },
  {
    id: 61,
    question: "How comfortable are you with taking on new responsibilities?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Very comfortable, I enjoy new challenges.",
        value: "Very comfortable, I enjoy new challenges.",
      },
      {
        label: "Comfortable, but I like to be prepared first.",
        value: "Comfortable, but I like to be prepared first.",
      },
      {
        label: "Somewhat comfortable, depending on the task.",
        value: "Somewhat comfortable, depending on the task.",
      },
      {
        label: "Uncomfortable, I prefer to stick to what I know.",
        value: "Uncomfortable, I prefer to stick to what I know.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Very comfortable, I enjoy new challenges.",
  },
  {
    id: 62,
    question: "What is your preferred work environment?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "A dynamic and fast-paced setting.",
        value: "A dynamic and fast-paced setting.",
      },
      {
        label: "A structured and organized environment.",
        value: "A structured and organized environment.",
      },
      {
        label: "A collaborative and supportive atmosphere.",
        value: "A collaborative and supportive atmosphere.",
      },
      {
        label: "A quiet and independent workspace.",
        value: "A quiet and independent workspace.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "A collaborative and supportive atmosphere.",
  },
  {
    id: 63,
    question: "How do you prioritize your work tasks?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Based on deadlines and urgency.",
        value: "Based on deadlines and urgency.",
      },
      {
        label: "According to the level of importance and impact.",
        value: "According to the level of importance and impact.",
      },
      {
        label: "By following a structured plan or schedule.",
        value: "By following a structured plan or schedule.",
      },
      {
        label: "In response to immediate demands or requests.",
        value: "In response to immediate demands or requests.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "According to the level of importance and impact.",
  },
  {
    id: 64,
    question: "What type of recognition do you value most at work?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Public acknowledgment and praise.",
        value: "Public acknowledgment and praise.",
      },
      {
        label: "Personal feedback and encouragement from peers.",
        value: "Personal feedback and encouragement from peers.",
      },
      {
        label: "Formal awards and certificates.",
        value: "Formal awards and certificates.",
      },
      {
        label: "Opportunities for career advancement.",
        value: "Opportunities for career advancement.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Opportunities for career advancement.",
  },
  {
    id: 65,
    question:
      "How do you handle tasks that you find less interesting or engaging?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Seek ways to make them more enjoyable or meaningful.",
        value: "Seek ways to make them more enjoyable or meaningful.",
      },
      {
        label: "Delegate them to others if possible.",
        value: "Delegate them to others if possible.",
      },
      {
        label: "Focus on completing them efficiently and effectively.",
        value: "Focus on completing them efficiently and effectively.",
      },
      {
        label: "Take breaks or find motivation to stay engaged.",
        value: "Take breaks or find motivation to stay engaged.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Focus on completing them efficiently and effectively.",
  },

  // Motivations
  {
    id: 66,
    question: "What drives you to achieve your goals?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Personal ambition and desire for success.",
        value: "Personal ambition and desire for success.",
      },
      {
        label: "External rewards and recognition.",
        value: "External rewards and recognition.",
      },
      {
        label: "The challenge and satisfaction of overcoming obstacles.",
        value: "The challenge and satisfaction of overcoming obstacles.",
      },
      {
        label: "The impact and contribution to others' success.",
        value: "The impact and contribution to others' success.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The challenge and satisfaction of overcoming obstacles.",
  },
  {
    id: 67,
    question: "How do you maintain motivation when facing long-term projects?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Set short-term goals and celebrate milestones.",
        value: "Set short-term goals and celebrate milestones.",
      },
      {
        label: "Focus on the overall outcome and benefits.",
        value: "Focus on the overall outcome and benefits.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek regular feedback and support from others.",
        value: "Seek regular feedback and support from others.",
      },
      {
        label: "Maintain a positive attitude and self-discipline.",
        value: "Maintain a positive attitude and self-discipline.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Set short-term goals and celebrate milestones.",
  },
  {
    id: 68,
    question: "What kind of challenges are you most motivated to tackle?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Complex problems that require creative solutions.",
        value: "Complex problems that require creative solutions.",
      },
      {
        label: "Tasks that involve collaboration and teamwork.",
        value: "Tasks that involve collaboration and teamwork.",
      },
      {
        label: "Projects with clear and measurable goals.",
        value: "Projects with clear and measurable goals.",
      },
      {
        label: "Opportunities for personal growth and development.",
        value: "Opportunities for personal growth and development.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Complex problems that require creative solutions.",
  },
  {
    id: 69,
    question:
      "How do you stay motivated during periods of low energy or productivity?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Take breaks and engage in activities that rejuvenate me.",
        value: "Take breaks and engage in activities that rejuvenate me.",
      },
      {
        label: "Set smaller, manageable tasks to regain momentum.",
        value: "Set smaller, manageable tasks to regain momentum.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek support or encouragement from colleagues or mentors.",
        value: "Seek support or encouragement from colleagues or mentors.",
      },
      {
        label: "Review and adjust my goals to align with my current state.",
        value: "Review and adjust my goals to align with my current state.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Set smaller, manageable tasks to regain momentum.",
  },
  {
    id: 70,
    question: "What role does feedback play in your motivation?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "It provides direction and helps me improve.",
        value: "It provides direction and helps me improve.",
      },
      {
        label: "It serves as validation for my efforts and progress.",
        value: "It serves as validation for my efforts and progress.",
      },
      {
        label: "It helps me stay accountable and focused on my goals.",
        value: "It helps me stay accountable and focused on my goals.",
      },
      {
        label: "It is less important compared to intrinsic motivation.",
        value: "It is less important compared to intrinsic motivation.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "It provides direction and helps me improve.",
  },

  // Decision-Making Style
  {
    id: 71,
    question: "What is your primary approach to decision-making?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Analyze all available information and options.",
        value: "Analyze all available information and options.",
      },
      {
        label: "Trust my instincts and intuition.",
        value: "Trust my instincts and intuition.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek input and opinions from others.",
        value: "Seek input and opinions from others.",
      },
      {
        label: "Follow established procedures and guidelines.",
        value: "Follow established procedures and guidelines.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Analyze all available information and options.",
  },
  {
    id: 72,
    question: "How do you handle decisions with limited information?",
    options: [
      {
        label:
          "Make the best decision possible with the information available.",
        value:
          "Make the best decision possible with the information available.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek additional information to reduce uncertainty.",
        value: "Seek additional information to reduce uncertainty.",
      },
      {
        label: "Consult with others to gain different perspectives.",
        value: "Consult with others to gain different perspectives.",
      },
      {
        label: "Delay the decision until more information is available.",
        value: "Delay the decision until more information is available.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Make the best decision possible with the information available.",
  },
  {
    id: 73,
    question: "When faced with a difficult decision, what do you prioritize?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "The potential impact and consequences of each option.",
        value: "The potential impact and consequences of each option.",
      },
      {
        label: "The opinions and advice of trusted individuals.",
        value: "The opinions and advice of trusted individuals.",
      },
      {
        label: "My own values and beliefs.",
        value: "My own values and beliefs.",
      },
      {
        label: "The speed and efficiency of making the decision.",
        value: "The speed and efficiency of making the decision.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "The potential impact and consequences of each option.",
  },
  {
    id: 74,
    question: "How do you evaluate the success of a decision you made?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Assess the outcomes and results compared to the objectives.",
        value: "Assess the outcomes and results compared to the objectives.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek feedback from others affected by the decision.",
        value: "Seek feedback from others affected by the decision.",
      },
      {
        label: "Reflect on the decision-making process and personal learning.",
        value: "Reflect on the decision-making process and personal learning.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Compare the decision to similar past decisions and their results.",
        value:
          "Compare the decision to similar past decisions and their results.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Assess the outcomes and results compared to the objectives.",
  },
  {
    id: 75,
    question: "What strategy do you use for making decisions under pressure?",
    options: [
      {
        label:
          "Quickly evaluate the most critical factors and make a decision.",
        value:
          "Quickly evaluate the most critical factors and make a decision.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Consult with others to gather input and make an informed choice.",
        value:
          "Consult with others to gather input and make an informed choice.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Prioritize key objectives and focus on the most important aspects.",
        value:
          "Prioritize key objectives and focus on the most important aspects.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Take a step back and take a moment to calm down before deciding.",
        value:
          "Take a step back and take a moment to calm down before deciding.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Quickly evaluate the most critical factors and make a decision.",
  },
  {
    id: 76,
    question:
      "How do you handle decisions that involve conflicting priorities?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Evaluate the importance of each priority and make a trade-off.",
        value: "Evaluate the importance of each priority and make a trade-off.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek input from others to help balance the priorities.",
        value: "Seek input from others to help balance the priorities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Focus on the long-term impact and make a decision accordingly.",
        value: "Focus on the long-term impact and make a decision accordingly.",
      },
      {
        label: "Address the most urgent priority first and then reassess.",
        value: "Address the most urgent priority first and then reassess.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Evaluate the importance of each priority and make a trade-off.",
  },
  {
    id: 77,
    question: "How do you stay inspired and motivated to be creative?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Expose myself to new experiences and perspectives.",
        value: "Expose myself to new experiences and perspectives.",
      },
      {
        label: "Set aside dedicated time for creative thinking.",
        value: "Set aside dedicated time for creative thinking.",
      },
      {
        label: "Engage in creative hobbies or side projects.",
        value: "Engage in creative hobbies or side projects.",
      },
      {
        label: "Collaborate with others who inspire me.",
        value: "Collaborate with others who inspire me.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Expose myself to new experiences and perspectives.",
  },
  {
    id: 78,
    question: "What do you do when a creative idea does not work as planned?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Analyze what went wrong and learn from the experience.",
        value: "Analyze what went wrong and learn from the experience.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek feedback and suggestions for improvement.",
        value: "Seek feedback and suggestions for improvement.",
      },
      {
        label: "Revise the idea and try again.",
        value: "Revise the idea and try again.",
      },
      {
        label: "Move on to a different idea and set the previous one aside.",
        value: "Move on to a different idea and set the previous one aside.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Analyze what went wrong and learn from the experience.",
  },
  {
    id: 79,
    question: "How do you evaluate the success of a creative project?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Assess whether the project met its goals and objectives.",
        value: "Assess whether the project met its goals and objectives.",
      },
      {
        label: "Gather feedback from users or stakeholders.",
        value: "Gather feedback from users or stakeholders.",
      },
      {
        label: "Measure the impact or results achieved.",
        value: "Measure the impact or results achieved.",
      },
      {
        label: "Reflect on the creative process and personal satisfaction.",
        value: "Reflect on the creative process and personal satisfaction.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Assess whether the project met its goals and objectives.",
  },
  {
    id: 80,
    question: "What role does risk-taking play in your creative process?",
    options: [
      {
        label:
          "I embrace risk-taking as a way to innovate and explore new ideas.",
        value:
          "I embrace risk-taking as a way to innovate and explore new ideas.",
      },
      {
        label: "I weigh the risks carefully and take calculated risks.",
        value: "I weigh the risks carefully and take calculated risks.",
      },
      {
        label: "I prefer to play it safe and stick to proven methods.",
        value: "I prefer to play it safe and stick to proven methods.",
      },
      {
        label: "I avoid risk-taking and focus on minimizing uncertainties.",
        value: "I avoid risk-taking and focus on minimizing uncertainties.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "I embrace risk-taking as a way to innovate and explore new ideas.",
  },
  {
    id: 81,
    question: "How do you encourage others to be more creative?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Create a supportive environment where ideas are welcomed.",
        value: "Create a supportive environment where ideas are welcomed.",
      },
      {
        label: "Provide opportunities for experimentation and innovation.",
        value: "Provide opportunities for experimentation and innovation.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Offer constructive feedback and recognition for creative efforts.",
        value:
          "Offer constructive feedback and recognition for creative efforts.",
      },
      {
        label: "Lead by example and demonstrate creative thinking.",
        value: "Lead by example and demonstrate creative thinking.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Create a supportive environment where ideas are welcomed.",
  },

  // Teamwork and Collaboration
  {
    id: 82,
    question: "How do you contribute to a team project?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Take on tasks that match my strengths and skills.",
        value: "Take on tasks that match my strengths and skills.",
      },
      {
        label: "Offer support and help others when needed.",
        value: "Offer support and help others when needed.",
      },
      {
        label: "Communicate effectively and share relevant information.",
        value: "Communicate effectively and share relevant information.",
      },
      {
        label: "Encourage and motivate team members.",
        value: "Encourage and motivate team members.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Communicate effectively and share relevant information.",
  },
  {
    id: 83,
    question: "What is your approach to resolving conflicts within a team?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Facilitate open dialogue and find common ground.",
        value: "Facilitate open dialogue and find common ground.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek a compromise that addresses everyone's concerns.",
        value: "Seek a compromise that addresses everyone's concerns.",
      },
      {
        label: "Involve a neutral third party to mediate.",
        value: "Involve a neutral third party to mediate.",
      },
      {
        label: "Address the conflict directly with those involved.",
        value: "Address the conflict directly with those involved.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Facilitate open dialogue and find common ground.",
  },
  {
    id: 84,
    question: "How do you ensure effective communication in a team setting?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Use clear and concise language.",
        value: "Use clear and concise language.",
      },
      {
        label: "Encourage regular updates and feedback.",
        value: "Encourage regular updates and feedback.",
      },
      {
        label: "Adapt communication style to the needs of the team.",
        value: "Adapt communication style to the needs of the team.",
      },
      {
        label: "Provide channels for open and honest communication.",
        value: "Provide channels for open and honest communication.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Encourage regular updates and feedback.",
  },
  {
    id: 85,
    question: "What strategies do you use to build trust within a team?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Be transparent and honest in all interactions.",
        value: "Be transparent and honest in all interactions.",
      },
      {
        label: "Follow through on commitments and promises.",
        value: "Follow through on commitments and promises.",
      },
      {
        label: "Show respect and value each team member's contributions.",
        value: "Show respect and value each team member's contributions.",
      },
      {
        label: "Encourage team bonding and positive relationships.",
        value: "Encourage team bonding and positive relationships.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Show respect and value each team member's contributions.",
  },
  {
    id: 86,
    question:
      "How do you handle situations where team members have different working styles?",
    options: [
      {
        label:
          "Encourage open discussions to understand and accommodate differences.",
        value:
          "Encourage open discussions to understand and accommodate differences.",
      },
      {
        label: "Adapt my working style to complement others.",
        value: "Adapt my working style to complement others.",
      },
      {
        label: "Establish clear guidelines and expectations for the team.",
        value: "Establish clear guidelines and expectations for the team.",
      },
      {
        label: "Assign tasks based on individual strengths and preferences.",
        value: "Assign tasks based on individual strengths and preferences.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Encourage open discussions to understand and accommodate differences.",
  },
  {
    id: 87,
    question: "What role do you typically take on in team meetings?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Facilitator, guiding the discussion and keeping it on track.",
        value: "Facilitator, guiding the discussion and keeping it on track.",
      },
      {
        label: "Contributor, providing input and ideas.",
        value: "Contributor, providing input and ideas.",
      },
      {
        label: "Observer, listening and supporting others' contributions.",
        value: "Observer, listening and supporting others' contributions.",
      },
      {
        label: "Coordinator, ensuring follow-up on action items and decisions.",
        value: "Coordinator, ensuring follow-up on action items and decisions.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Contributor, providing input and ideas.",
  },
  {
    id: 88,
    question: "How do you manage workload distribution within a team?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Assign tasks based on individual skills and capacities.",
        value: "Assign tasks based on individual skills and capacities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Ensure an equitable distribution of tasks among team members.",
        value: "Ensure an equitable distribution of tasks among team members.",
      },
      {
        label: "Discuss and agree on task distribution with the team.",
        value: "Discuss and agree on task distribution with the team.",
      },
      {
        label: "Monitor workloads regularly and adjust as needed.",
        value: "Monitor workloads regularly and adjust as needed.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Assign tasks based on individual skills and capacities.",
  },
  {
    id: 89,
    question:
      "How do you handle a situation where a team member is not contributing effectively?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Discuss the issue privately and provide support or guidance.",
        value: "Discuss the issue privately and provide support or guidance.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Provide additional resources or training to improve contribution.",
        value:
          "Provide additional resources or training to improve contribution.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Adjust the team member's responsibilities to better fit their strengths.",
        value:
          "Adjust the team member's responsibilities to better fit their strengths.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Address the issue in a team meeting to find a collective solution.",
        value:
          "Address the issue in a team meeting to find a collective solution.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Discuss the issue privately and provide support or guidance.",
  },
  {
    id: 90,
    question: "How do you celebrate team successes?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Organize team gatherings or events.",
        value: "Organize team gatherings or events.",
      },
      {
        label: "Recognize individual and team contributions publicly.",
        value: "Recognize individual and team contributions publicly.",
      },
      {
        label: "Provide rewards or incentives for achieving goals.",
        value: "Provide rewards or incentives for achieving goals.",
      },
      {
        label: "Share success stories and lessons learned with the team.",
        value: "Share success stories and lessons learned with the team.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Recognize individual and team contributions publicly.",
  },

  // Interpersonal Skills
  {
    id: 90,
    question: "How do you usually respond to a conflict with a colleague?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Address the issue directly and seek a resolution.",
        value: "Address the issue directly and seek a resolution.",
      },
      {
        label: "Avoid confrontation and let it resolve on its own.",
        value: "Avoid confrontation and let it resolve on its own.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek mediation from a third party.",
        value: "Seek mediation from a third party.",
      },
      {
        label: "Express my frustrations in a private setting.",
        value: "Express my frustrations in a private setting.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Address the issue directly and seek a resolution.",
  },
  {
    id: 91,
    question: "What is your approach to giving constructive feedback?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Provide specific examples and focus on improvement.",
        value: "Provide specific examples and focus on improvement.",
      },
      {
        label:
          "Highlight the positives before mentioning areas for improvement.",
        value:
          "Highlight the positives before mentioning areas for improvement.",
      },
      {
        label: "Be direct and honest, regardless of how it might be received.",
        value: "Be direct and honest, regardless of how it might be received.",
      },
      {
        label: "Offer feedback only when asked for it.",
        value: "Offer feedback only when asked for it.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Provide specific examples and focus on improvement.",
  },
  {
    id: 92,
    question: "How do you build rapport with new team members?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Engage in casual conversations and find common interests.",
        value: "Engage in casual conversations and find common interests.",
      },
      {
        label: "Observe their behavior and adapt my communication style.",
        value: "Observe their behavior and adapt my communication style.",
      },
      {
        label: "Offer help and support to integrate them into the team.",
        value: "Offer help and support to integrate them into the team.",
      },
      {
        label: "Share my experiences and background to establish a connection.",
        value: "Share my experiences and background to establish a connection.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Engage in casual conversations and find common interests.",
  },
  {
    id: 93,
    question: "How do you handle team disagreements?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Facilitate a discussion to understand different viewpoints.",
        value: "Facilitate a discussion to understand different viewpoints.",
      },
      {
        label: "Choose a side and advocate for it.",
        value: "Choose a side and advocate for it.",
      },
      {
        label: "Avoid the disagreement and let the team sort it out.",
        value: "Avoid the disagreement and let the team sort it out.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek a compromise that satisfies all parties involved.",
        value: "Seek a compromise that satisfies all parties involved.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer:
      "Facilitate a discussion to understand different viewpoints.",
  },
  {
    id: 94,
    question: "What is your strategy for effective team communication?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Ensure clarity and regular updates on project status.",
        value: "Ensure clarity and regular updates on project status.",
      },
      {
        label: "Encourage open dialogue and feedback among team members.",
        value: "Encourage open dialogue and feedback among team members.",
      },
      {
        label: "Use various communication tools to keep everyone informed.",
        value: "Use various communication tools to keep everyone informed.",
      },
      {
        label: "Schedule regular meetings to discuss progress and challenges.",
        value: "Schedule regular meetings to discuss progress and challenges.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Encourage open dialogue and feedback among team members.",
  },

  // Learning Preferences
  {
    id: 95,
    question: "What learning method do you find most effective for you?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Hands-on practice and real-world application.",
        value: "Hands-on practice and real-world application.",
      },
      {
        label: "Reading and reviewing detailed instructional materials.",
        value: "Reading and reviewing detailed instructional materials.",
      },
      {
        label: "Listening to lectures or audio recordings.",
        value: "Listening to lectures or audio recordings.",
      },
      {
        label: "Participating in discussions and group activities.",
        value: "Participating in discussions and group activities.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Hands-on practice and real-world application.",
  },
  {
    id: 96,
    question: "How do you prefer to receive new information?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Through interactive and engaging activities.",
        value: "Through interactive and engaging activities.",
      },
      {
        label: "Via written documents and detailed guides.",
        value: "Via written documents and detailed guides.",
      },
      {
        label: "In verbal explanations and presentations.",
        value: "In verbal explanations and presentations.",
      },
      {
        label: "By observing demonstrations and examples.",
        value: "By observing demonstrations and examples.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Through interactive and engaging activities.",
  },
  {
    id: 97,
    question: "What type of feedback helps you learn best?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Constructive and actionable feedback.",
        value: "Constructive and actionable feedback.",
      },
      {
        label: "Positive reinforcement and encouragement.",
        value: "Positive reinforcement and encouragement.",
      },
      {
        label: "Detailed explanations of mistakes and how to correct them.",
        value: "Detailed explanations of mistakes and how to correct them.",
      },
      {
        label: "General comments on performance.",
        value: "General comments on performance.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Constructive and actionable feedback.",
  },
  {
    id: 98,
    question: "When acquiring new knowledge, which approach do you prefer?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Learning through trial and error.",
        value: "Learning through trial and error.",
      },
      {
        label: "Following a structured curriculum or course.",
        value: "Following a structured curriculum or course.",
      },
      {
        label: "Receiving mentorship and guidance from experts.",
        value: "Receiving mentorship and guidance from experts.",
      },
      {
        label: "Engaging in self-directed study and research.",
        value: "Engaging in self-directed study and research.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Following a structured curriculum or course.",
  },
  {
    id: 99,
    question:
      "How do you adapt your learning strategies when faced with complex material?",
    options: [
      {
        label: "Break down the material into smaller, manageable sections.",
        value: "Break down the material into smaller, manageable sections.",
      },
      {
        label: "Seek additional resources or alternative explanations.",
        value: "Seek additional resources or alternative explanations.",
      },
      {
        label: "Discuss the material with peers or mentors for clarification.",
        value: "Discuss the material with peers or mentors for clarification.",
      },
      {
        label: "Review and practice regularly to reinforce understanding.",
        value: "Review and practice regularly to reinforce understanding.",
      },
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Break down the material into smaller, manageable sections.",
  },
];
